blapage.com 2018-10-14

# Privacy Policy | Web Tips, SEO, Personal Computers

## [Privacy Policy](http://www.blapage.com/privacy-policy "Privacy Policy")

**Our Commitment To Privacy**

Your privacy is important to us. To better protect your privacy we provide this notice explaining our online information practices and the choices you can make about the way your information is collected and used. To make this notice easy to find, we make it available from every page where personally identifiable information may be requested.

**The Information We Collect:**

This notice applies to all information collected or submitted on the BlaPage website. On some pages, you can order products, make requests, and register to receive materials. The types of personal information collected at these pages are:

Email address  
IP information

**The Way We Use Information**

We do not share this information with outside parties except to the extent necessary when the law requires us to comply.

**Advertising**

We also use third party advertisements to support our site. Some of these may use technology such as cookies from advertisers (such as Google through the Google AdSense program).

Finally, we never use or share the personally identifiable information provided to us online in ways unrelated to the ones described above without also providing you an opportunity to opt-out or otherwise prohibit such unrelated uses.

**Our Commitment To Data Security**

To prevent unauthorized access, maintain data accuracy, and ensure the correct use of information, we have put in place appropriate physical, electronic, and managerial procedures to safeguard and secure the information we collect online.

**How To Contact Us**

Should you have other questions or concerns about these privacy policies, please contact us from our contact form.
